Tiffany Bouchard

Full-Stack Developer

I am fueled by challenge and driven to build amazing experiences for people, with people. I strive to use my curiosity and passion for technology to actualize innovative and creative concepts while applying beautiful UX and technical design.

Experience

05 - 07/2020

Student - General Assembly Toronto

- -Full time student in the Software Engineering Immersive program including over 400 hours of training over 12 weeks.
- -Completed three individual and collaborative full-stack projects incorporating technical skills learned
 - Chef Technical blog platform for tutorials
 - How Risky? A COVID-19 activity risk assessment app
 - Forkpitch A review platform for Pitchfork music reviews

02/2019 - 01/2019

Server & Supervisor - Otto's Berlin Döner

- -Performed end of day tasks including cash-out routine and counting till
- -Ensured front-of-house staff provided high-quality customer service and promoted a positive team atmosphere
- -Built relationships with customers, co-workers and management

03/2015 - 11/2018

Lifeguard, Instructor and Coach – City of Toronto

- -Promoted a safe environment and provided outstanding customer service to patrons
- -Displayed the ability to act quickly and calmly under pressure individually and as a team
- -Cultivated positive relationships with participants by interacting with them during classes and practices

Contact

tiffnbouchard@gmail.com 647-381-1429

linkedin.com/in/tiffany-bouchard/ github.com/tiffbouchard tiffbouchard.com

Education

Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly Toronto 2020

Philosophy & Criminology (BA) University of Toronto 2016-2020

Languages & Frameworks

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, jQuery, Express, Bootstrap, React, Next.js, Python, Django, SQL, Mongoose

Tools

Git, GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, Vercel, Command Line, Figma

Databases

PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Methodologies/Techniques

Object Oriented Programming, MVC Pattern, AJAX, Responsive Design, User Stories, Wireframing, ERD's

Side Projects/Works in Progress

- -OJOS eCommerce shop
- -iome Portfolio task management app built with a team of developers and UX designers
- LinenWay Redesign/rebuild eCommerce site for client with a team of developers and UX designers